Whatever happened to Snow White?
Happily Ever After is a family, animation, fantasy film directed by John Howley.
In the aftermath of her more famous adventure, Snow White must team up with the dwarves' seven female
cousins to battle the late Evil Queen's warlock brother and rescue the captured Prince.
Snow White (voice), played by Irene Cara.
Lord Maliss (voice), played by Malcolm McDowell.
The Looking Glass (voice), played by Dom DeLuise.
Muddy (voice), played by Carol Channing.
Mother Nature (voice), played by Phyllis Diller.
Blossom (voice), played by Zsa Zsa Gabor.
Happily Ever After (originally released as Snow White: The Adventure Continues in the Philippines) is a 1989 animated musical fantasy film directed by John Howley, and
starring the voices of Dom DeLuise, Malcolm McDowell, Phyllis Diller, Zsa Zsa Gabor, Ed Asner, Sally Kellerman, Irene Cara, Carol Channing and Tracey Ullman.
The film serves as a direct sequel to the Snow White fairy tale, wherein the titular heroine and the Prince are about to
be married, but a new threat appears in the form of the late Evil Queen's vengeful brother, Lord Maliss.
The plot replaces the Dwarfs with female cousins called the
Dwarfelles, who aid Snow White against Maliss.
Happily Ever After is unrelated to Filmation's fellow A Snow White Christmas, a 1980 TV
special in which continuity is deliberately and consequently ignored.
Following extensive legal troubles with The Walt Disney Company, it had a poor
financial and critical reception following its wide release in 1993.
A video game adaptation was released in 1994.
The film explores themes of prince, musical, dragon, based on fairy tale.